import { Deck } from './deck';
import { createCard } from './card';

const frenchCards = createFrenchCards();
const frenchDeck = Object.assign(Object.create(Deck), {
    name: 'French',
    description: 'A deck to learn 10 basic French words',
    dueDate: 'Next Week',
    category: 'Languages',
    currentCard: 0,
    cardCount: 0,
    cards: frenchCards,
});
    
function createFrenchCards() {

    const frenchCardOne = {
        question: 'How do you say \'a man\' in French?',
        answer: 'un homme',
    };
    
    const frenchCardTwo = {
        question: 'How do you say \'a tree\' in French?',
        answer: 'un arbre',
    };
    
    const frenchCardThree = {
        question: 'How do you say \'a chair\' in French?',
        answer: 'une chaise',
    };
    
    const frenchCardFour = {
        question: 'How do you say \'a computer\' in French?',
        answer: 'un ordinateur',
    };
    
    const frenchCardFive = {
        question: 'How do you say \'a window\' in French?',
        answer: 'une fenêtre',
    };
    
    const frenchCardSix = {
        question: 'How do you say \'a school\' in French?',
        answer: 'une école',
    };
    
    const frenchCardSeven = {
        question: 'How do you say \'a menu\' in French?',
        answer: 'une carte',
    };
    
    const frenchCardEight = {
        question: 'How do you say \'a doctor\' in French?',
        answer: 'une voiture',
    };
    
    const frenchCardNine = {
        question: 'How do you say \'a shirt\' in French?',
        answer: 'une chemise',
    };
    
    const frenchCardTen = {
        question: 'How do you say \'a party\' in French?',
        answer: 'une fête',
    };

    const frenchCards = [frenchCardOne, frenchCardTwo, frenchCardThree, 
                    frenchCardFour, frenchCardFive, frenchCardSix, 
                    frenchCardSeven, frenchCardEight, frenchCardNine,
                    frenchCardTen];
    
        frenchCards.forEach((card) => {
        card = createCard(card);
    });
    return frenchCards;
}
export const preBuiltDecks = [frenchDeck];